[
  {

    "question":"Spor Sorusu?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Spor Sorusu   1 ?",
    "answer":"Yes"
  },
  {

    "question":"Spor Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Spor Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Spor Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"Yes"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"Yes"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"No"
  }
,
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   1 ?",
    "answer":"Yes"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu  2   ?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   3  ?",
    "answer":"No"
  },
  {

    "question":"Bilim Sorusu   4  ?",
    "answer":"Yes"
  }

]
